Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. Review Board Records, 1947-1976, 1987-1995 RL.00745
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Meetings Series, 1950-1974.
  - Phillips Petroleum Co. (Box 24)
    - Summaries, 1967-1973, 7 folders (Box 24)
    - Minutes, 1963, 1965, 1969-1971, 5 folders (Box 24)
  - Phillips Petroleum, Minutes, 1972 (Box 25)
  - Pittsburgh Plate Glass
    - Summaries, 1962 (Box 25)
    - Minutes, 1961-1962 (Box 25)
  - Pro-phy-lac-tic Brush Co.
    - Summaries
      - Perma-Grip, 1963 (Box 25)
      - Pro-jet Stream, 1967-1968 (Box 25)
      - Toothbrush, 1963-1968 (Box 25)
    - Minutes, 1963, 1966 (Box 25)
  - Publicker Distillers Products Inc.
    - Summaries
      - Inver House Scotch, 1974 (Box 25)
      - Kulov Imported Vodka, 1974 (Box 25)
  - Purolator Products, Inc.
    - Summaries, 1962-1964 (Box 25)
    - Minutes, 1956-1962 (Box 25)
  - RCA Corp.
    - Summaries
      - Electronics systems, 1970-1971 (Box 25)
      - Computer systems, 1970-1971 (Box 25)
      - Consumer electronics, 1971-1974 (Box 25)
      - Corporate, 1970-1974 (Box 25)
      - General, 1961-1966 (Box 25)
      - Government and commercial systems, 1972-1974 (Box 25)
      - Graphic systems, 1970 (Box 25)
      - Sales corporation, 1966-1971 (Box 25)
    - Minutes, 1959-1964, 1967 (Box 25)
  - Reader's Digest
    - Summaries
      - Digest Music Inc., 1964 (Box 25)
      - Domestic promotion (space sales), 1961-1974 (Box 25)
  - Reader's Digest (Box 26)
    - Summaries, Retail circulation, 1961-1974 (Box 26)
    - Minutes, 1957-1963, 1969, 3 folders (Box 26)
  - Religion in American Life, Minutes, 1962-1963 (Box 26)
  - Reynolds Metals Co.
    - Summaries, Reynolds Wrap, 1972-1974 (Box 26)
    - Minutes, 1973 (Box 26)
  - R.J. Reynolds Foods, Inc.
    - Summaries
      - Chun King canned line, 1968-1972 (Box 26)
      - Chun King frozen line, 1968-1972 (Box 26)
      - College Inn, 1969-1972 (Box 26)
      - My-T-Fine dessert line, 1971-1972 (Box 26)
    - Minutes, 1969 (Box 26)
  - Rolex Watches USA, Inc., Summaries, 1968-1974 (Box 26)
  - Rowntree and Co., Minutes, 1960-1961, 2 folders (Box 26)
  - Saga Mink, Minutes, 1970 (Box 26)
  - Samsonite Corp. (Box 27)
    - Summaries
      - Furniture, 1971-1972 (Box 27)
      - Luggage, 1971-1974 (Box 27)
      - Toys, 1971-1972 (Box 27)
    - Minutes, 1974 (Box 27)
  - Scandinavian Mink Association, Summaries, 1973-1974 (Box 27)
  - Scientific American, Minutes, 1974 (Box 27)
  - Scott Paper Co.
    - Summaries
      - Confidets sanitary napkin, 1962-1968 (Box 27)
      - Corporate, 1970 (Box 27)
      - Cut-Rite Aluminum Foil, 1963-1964 (Box 27)
      - Cut-Rite Plastic Bags, 1964-1968 (Box 27)
      - Cut-Rite Plastic Wrap, 1963-1968 (Box 27)
      - Cut-Rite Wax Paper and Bags, 1961-1969 (Box 27)
      - Facial and Bathroom Tissues, 1964-1974 (Box 27)
      - Family Napkins, 1961-1970 (Box 27)
      - Job Squad Disposable Towels, 1973-1974 (Box 27)
      - Scotkins, 1961-1970 (Box 27)
      - Scott Cups, 1964-1967 (Box 27)
      - Scott Placemats, 1962-1969 (Box 27)
      - Scott Tissues, 1961-1974 (Box 27)
      - Scott Umbrella (signature brands), 1971 (Box 27)
      - Scotties Facial Tissue, 1961-1974 (Box 27)
      - ScotTowels, 1961-1974 (Box 27)
      - Soft-Weve Toilet Tissue, 1961-1974 (Box 27)
      - Viva Napkins, 1966-1970 (Box 27)
      - Viva Towels, 1967-1970 (Box 27)
  - Scott Paper Co. (Box 28)
    - Summaries
      - Windblossoms facial tissue, 1974 (Box 28)
      - Wonder Wrap, 1961 (Box 28)
      - New Products, 1967-1968 (Box 28)
    - Minutes, 1969-1970, 2 folders
      - Confidets sanitary napkin, 1962-1963, 1966 (Box 28)
      - Cut-Rite, 1956-1957, 1961-1963, 2 folders (Box 28)
      - Family Napkins and Scotkins, 1955-1958, 1960-1963, 2 folders (Box 28)
      - Great Scot! Men's Handkerchief, 1957 (Box 28)
      - Scott Tissue, 1956-1958, 1960-1961, 2 folders (Box 28)
      - Scotties Facial Tissue, 1956, 1958, 1961 (Box 28)
      - ScotTowels, 1957, 1961-1962, 1964 (Box 28)
  - Scott Paper Co. (Box 29)
    - Minutes
      - Soft-Weve Toilet Tissue, 1957-1958, 1961-1963 (Box 29)
      - Three-Day Dish Towels, 1957 (Box 29)
      - Various Products, 1956, 1958-1959, 1961-1964 (Box 29)
      - John Monsarrat, 1964-1965, 3 folders (Box 29)
  - Scripto International, Minutes, 1957-1958 (Box 29)
  - Seagrams
    - Summaries
      - 100 Pipers Scotch Whiskey, 1968-1970 (Box 29)
      - Antique Bourbon, 1967-1974 (Box 29)
      - Barton and Guestier Wines, 1970 (Box 29)
      - Four Roses Distillers Co., 1971 (Box 29)
      - Henry McKenna Bourbon, 1968-1970 (Box 29)
      - Mattingly and Moore Bourbon, 1968-1974 (Box 29)
      - Mumm's Champagne, 1970 (Box 29)
      - Nectarose Vin Rose D'anjou, 1970 (Box 29)
      - Paul Jones Whiskey, 1968-1974 (Box 29)
      - Rarc Antique Bourbon, 1970-1974 (Box 29)
      - Ronrico Rum, 1967-1974 (Box 29)
      - Wolfschmidt Vodka, 1970-1973 (Box 29)
    - Minutes, 1969, 1973, 2 folders (Box 29)
  - Shell Oil Co., Minutes, 1956-1959 (Box 30)
  - Simmons Co.
    - Summaries, 1974 (Box 30)
    - Minutes, 1973 (Box 30)
  - Singer Co.
    - Summaries, 1964-1972 (Box 30)
    - Minutes, 1964-1965 (Box 30)
  - Squibb Beech-Nut Inc.
    - Summaries
      - Beech-Nut Baby Foods, 1968-1971 (Box 30)
      - Broxodent Electric Toothbrush, 1970-1971 (Box 30)
      - Sweeta, 1968-1969 (Box 30)
    - Minutes, 1970 (Box 30)
  - Spiegal Industries Corp., Summaries, 1974 (Box 30)
  - Standard Brands Inc.
    - Summaries
      - Chase and Sanborn Coffee, 1961-1974 (Box 30)
      - Fleischmann's Yeast, 1961-1974 (Box 30)
      - Insta-Jel, 1968 (Box 30)
      - Instant Chase and Sanborn, 1961-1971 (Box 30)
      - Instant Tender Leaf Tea, 1961-1963 (Box 30)
      - Peanut Crisps, 1968 (Box 30)
      - Planters Nuts, 1962-1974 (Box 30)
      - Planters Oil, 1962-1974 (Box 30)
      - Planters Peanut Butter, 1962-1969 (Box 30)
      - Putnam's Inn Coffee, 1968-1971 (Box 30)
    - Minutes, 1964-1966, 1973, 3 folders (Box 30)
  - Standard Brands (Box 31)
    - Minutes
      - Chase and Sanborn Coffee, 1961-1963, 2 folders (Box 31)
      - Fleischmann's Yeast, 1956, 1961-1963, 2 folders (Box 31)
      - Instant Chase and Sanborn, 1960-1963 (Box 31)
      - Nut Division, 1955-1957 (Box 31)
      - Planters Peanuts (various products), 1961-1963, 2 folders (Box 31)
      - Tender Leaf Tea, 1956-1963 (Box 31)
  - Stouffer Corporation, Minutes, 1958-1959 (Box 31)
  - Sylvannia Electric Products, Inc., Minutes, 1956-1959 (Box 31)
  - Textron, Inc., Minutes, 1969 (Box 31)
  - Textron, Inc., Minutes, 1971-1972, 1974, 3 folders (Box 32)
  - J Walter Thompson Co.
    - Minutes
      - x1963 (Box 32)
      - John Monsarrat, member, JWT house ad campaign, 1964-1965 (Box 32)
  - United States Brewers Association
    - Summaries, 1961-1965 (Box 32)
    - Minutes, 1956, 1960-1963 (Box 32)
  - United States Lines
    - Summaries, S.S. United States, 1962-1969 (Box 32)
    - Minutes
      - x 1953-1963, 3 folders (Box 32)
      - Freight/Corporate, 1968 (Box 32)
      - John Monsarrat, 1964-1965 (Box 32)
  - United States Marine Corps
    - Summaries, 1964, 1973-1974 (Box 32)
    - Minutes, 1962-1964 (Box 32)
  - United States Marine Corps, Minutes, 1974, 2 folders (Box 33)
  - United States Playing Card Co.
    - Summaries. 1961-1970 (Box 33)
    - Minutes, 1953-1963, 1965, 2 folders (Box 33)
  - Ward Tip Top White Bread Baking Co., Minutes, 1958, 1959 (Box 33)
  - Warner Lambert
    - Summaries
      - American Chicle Division
        - Breath Pleasers, 1973 (Box 33)
        - Chiclets, 1972-1974 (Box 33)
        - Clorets, 1970-1974 (Box 33)
        - New Products, 1973 (Box 33)
      - Formula S, 1962-1964 (Box 33)
      - Lasting Beauty, 1970 (Box 33)
      - Listerine Antibacterial Acne Scrub, 1973-1974 (Box 33a)
      - Listerine Antiseptic, 1963-1974 (Box 33a)
      - Listerine Antiseptic Throat Lozenges, 1966-1974 (Box 33a)
      - Listerine Breath Fresheners, 1972-1973 (Box 33a)
      - Listerine Breath Spray, 1970-1971 (Box 33a)
      - Listerine Cold Tablets, 1969-1970 (Box 33a)
      - Listerine Family Cough Medicine, 1963 (Box 33a)
      - Listermint Mouthwash, 1973-1974 (Box 33a)
      - Listerol Spray disinfectant, 1973-1974 (Box 33a)
      - Product X, 1963 (Box 33a)
      - Reef Mouthwash, 1966-1968 (Box 33a)
    - Minutes
      - x 1962-1963, 2 folders (Box 33a)
      - Listerine, 1974 (Box 33a)
  - Warner Lambert (Box 34)
    - Minutes
      - Listerine Lozenges, 1974 (Box 34)
      - Listerol, 1974 (Box 34)
      - John Monsarrat, 1962-1964, 2 folders (Box 34)
  - Washington Gas Light Co.
    - Summaries, 1969-1971 (Box 34)
    - Minutes, 1969 (Box 34)
  - Wedgwood Inc., Summaries, 1974 (Box 34)
  - J.B. Williams, Minutes, 1955-1957 (Box 34)
  - Wool Bureau, Minutes, 1956-1960 (Box 34)
  - W.F. Young
    - Summaries
      - Absorbine Arthritis Pain Lotion, 1967-1974 (Box 34)
      - Absorbine Jr., Absorbine Foot Powder, 1961-1974 (Box 34)
      - Absorbine veterinary liniment, 1963-1974 (Box 34)
    - Minutes, 1955-1963, 1970, 4 folders (Box 34)
- 2019 Addition, 1987-1995; 1
  - 20th Century Fox, 1988-1989 (Box A1)
  - Acme Stores, 1988 (Box A1)
  - American Hawaii Cruises, 1988 (Box A1)
  - Ames Department Stores, 1990 (Box A1)
  - Atlanta Office, 1994 (Box A1)
  - Bally's/Health and Tennis Corporation (HTC), 1990; 2 folders (Box A1)
  - Baskin-Robbins, 1988 (Box A1)
  - Bell Atlantic, 1988-1994; 8 folders (Box A1)
  - Bell Atlantic--Project Utopia, 1989 (Box A1)
  - Chesebrough-Pond's, 1993 (Box A1)
  - Chevron, 1988-1990 (Box A1)
  - Circuit City, 1990 (Box A1)
  - Citibank, 1992-1993 (Box A1)
  - Clairol, 1993; 2 folders (Box A1)
  - Del Taco, 1988-1990 (Box A1)
  - Discover Card, 1987 (Box A1)
  - Eli Lilly, 1989-1990; 2 folders (Box A1)
  - Fisher-Price, 1988-1990 (Box A1)
  - Ford, 1989-1990; 2 folders (Box A1)
  - Ford/Citibank Card, 1994 (Box A1)
  - Freddie Mac, 1989; 5 folders (Box A1)
  - General--Advertising Planning Methods, 1987 (Box A1)
  - General--Business Review Boards philosophy, 1991-1994 (Box A1)
  - General--Review Board policies, forms, etc., 1988 (Box A1)
  - Gerber, 1988-1990 (Box A2)
  - Goodyear, 1989-1993; 5 folders (Box A2)
  - Jenny Craig, 1990-1991 (Box A2)
  - Kaiser Permanente, 1988-1989 (Box A2)
  - Kellogg, 1989-1990; 3 folders (Box A2)
  - Kellogg Canada, 1994; 2 folders (Box A2)
  - Kentucky Fried Chicken, 1988-1989; 2 folders (Box A2)
  - Kodak, 1988-1993; 8 folders (Box A2)
  - Kraft, 1988-1994; 4 folders (Box A2)
  - Kraft Canada, 1994 (Box A2)
  - Labatt Breweries (Canada), 1992 (Box A2)
  - Lever/Lipton, 1993-1994 (Box A2)
  - McDonnell-Douglas, 1988-1990; 4 folders (Box A2)
  - McDonnell-Douglas, 1990 (Box A3)
  - Mexicana Airlines, 1988-1990; 2 folders (Box A3)
  - Miller Brewing, 1988-1994; 2 folders (Box A3)
  - Motorola, 1994 (Box A3)
  - Nestle, 1988-1993; 7 folders (Box A3)
  - Norfold Southern, 1987-1990; 3 folders (Box A3)
  - Northern Telecom, 1988-1994; 7 folders (Box A3)
  - Northwestern Mutual Life Insurance, 1988-1990 (Box A3)
  - Orkin, 1988-1994; 4 folders (Box A3)
  - Oscar Mayer, 1988-1994; 4 folders (Box A3)
  - Paramount Home Video, 1988-1989 (Box A3)
  - Payless Drug Stores, 1993 (Box A3)
  - Prodigy, 1990-1993; 5 folders (Box A3)
  - Quaker Oats, 1987-1990; 3 folders (Box A3)
  - Quaker Oats Pet Division, 1989 (Box A3)
  - Reynolds Metals, 1988-1989; 2 folders (Box A3)
  - Reynolds Metals, 1989-1993; 2 folders (Box A4)
  - Reynolds Metals--Brand Review, 1988; 2 folders (Box A4)
  - Seagrams, 1988; 3 folders (Box A4)
  - Society Corporation, 1993 (Box A4)
  - Southland/7-Eleven, 1989-1994; 2 folders (Box A4)
  - Speedy Muffler King, 1990 (Box A4)
  - Sprint, 1988-1993; 6 folders (Box A4)
  - Sprint--Bill Esry briefing, 1989; 2 folders (Box A4)
  - Stuart Anderson Restaurants, 1989-1990 (Box A4)
  - Sun Microsystems, 1990 (Box A4)
  - Tenneco, 1989 (Box A4)
  - Toys R Us, 1993 (Box A4)
  - U.S. Department of Housing and Urban Development (HUD), 1993-1994 (Box A4)
  - U.S. Marine Corps, 1988-1995; 4 folders (Box A4)
  - Unilever, 1988-1989; 2 folders (Box A4)
  - Van Den Bergh Foods (Ragu), 1990-1994; 3 folders (Box A4)
  - Vons/Pavilions, 1988-1990; 3 folders (Box A4)
  - Walker Manufacturing, 1990; 2 folders (Box A4)
  - Wall Street Journal, 1990 (Box A5)
  - Warner-Lambert, 1988-1993; 7 folders (Box A5)
  - White Castle, 1995 (Box A5)